Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  - General Correspondence, 1895-1935. (Box 1-7)
    - General Correspondence: Fo-J, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 3:1-276)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Paul "May" L. Gillian, Washington, D.C., 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:39)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Sheb Gillespi, Bluefield, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:40)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. C. Gillispie, Temperanceville, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:41)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Fain Gillock, Washington, D.C., 1932., 5 items. (Box-folder 3:42)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Howard C. Gilmer, Pulaski, Virginia, 1918-1924., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:43)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. C. Gilmer, Pulaski, Virginia, 1926-1932., 12 items. (Box-folder 3:44)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Kenneth N. Gilpin, Richmond, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:45)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. P. Gladding, Oak Hall, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:46)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John W Gladding, Franklin City, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:47)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Roy Gladding, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:48)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mary Ann Gladstone, Parksley, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:49)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. P. Glasgow, Roanoke, Virginia, 1928-1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:50)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. Carter Glass, 1920., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:51)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Fairy M. Glenn, Saxis, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:52)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Charlie Godwin, Sanford, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:53)
      - Correspondence from Jos. M. Goldsmith, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:54)
      - Correspondence from W. S. Gooch, University, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:55)
      - Correspondence from John C. Goode, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:56)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Morton G. Goode, Dinwiddie, Virginia, 3 items. (Box-folder 3:57)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. B. Goodridge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:58)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William A. R. Goodwin, Richmond, Virginia, 1931-1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:59)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. O'Conor Goolrick, State Senator, 13th District, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1918-1928., 11 items. (Box-folder 3:60)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. L. Gordon, Louisa, Virginia, 1930., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:61)
      - Correspondence from J. S. Gordy, Mappsville and Bloxom, Virginia, 1905-1911., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:62)
      - Correspondence from John F. Gouldman, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1918., 6 items. (Box-folder 3:63)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John D. Grant, Accomac, Virginia, 1927-1934., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:64)
      - Correspondence from P. L. Grant, Rich-Square, North Carolina, 1911., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:65)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Wilson Grant, Catawba Sanatorium, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:66)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James H. C. Grasty, Staunton, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:67)
      - Correspondence from J. Willie Green, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:68)
      - Correspondence from J. Willie Green, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:69)
      - Correspondence from Geo. O. Greene, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:70)
      - Duplicate correspondence to P. W. Gregory, Washington, D.C., 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:71)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. T. Gresham, Norfolk, Virginia, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:72)
      - Correspondence from Robert J. Gresham, Senatobia, Mississippi, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:73)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. E. Griffin, Buckingham County, Virginia, 1925-1927., 8 items. (Box-folder 3:74)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mr. Grigsby, Lebanon, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:75)
      - Correspondence from R. M. Grizzard, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:76)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George Groton, Parksley, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:77)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. A. Grubbs, Shacklesfords. Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:78)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lottie Grossners, Schenectady, New York, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:79)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. T. C. Guerrant, Danville and Winston-Salem, Virginia, 1918, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:80)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Gunby and Company, Salisbury, Maryland, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:81)
      - Correspondence from L. Guy, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:82)
      - Correspondence from E. G., 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:83)
      - Correspondence from H. Clay Hack of Maryland, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:84)
      - Correspondence from W. B. Halslip, High Point, North Carolina, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:85)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Charles Hall, Rio Vista, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:86)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. Madison Hall, Tappahannock, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:87)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Henry C. Hall, Sanford, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:88)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Howard Hall, President of WCTU [Women's Christian Temperance Union], Cherlton, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:89)
      - Correspondence from James A. Hall, Montross, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:90)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. C. Hall, Parksley, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:91)
      - Correspondence from S. C. Hall, Hallwood, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:92)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Sidney B. Hall, Richmond, Virginia, 1932-1934., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:93)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Wilbur C. Hall, Leesburg, Virginia, 1925-1934., 13 items. (Box-folder 3:94)
      - Correspondence from O. M. Hallett, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:95)
      - Correspondence from "Cousin Hallie," Blenheim, Virginia, 1911, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:96)
      - Correspondence with P. B. Halligan, Carson, Virginia, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:97)
      - Telegram from Hallwood National Bank, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:98)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Norman Hamilton, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1929-1932., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:99)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. B. Handy, Richmond, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:100)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with O. V. Hanger, 1925, 1928., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:101)
      - Correspondence from J. D. Hank, Jr., Assistant Attorney General of Virginia, Richmond, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:102)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Katherine Hardenburg, Keller, Virginia, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:103)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Porter Hardy, Painter, Virginia, 1913., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:104)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Colie Harmon, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1911., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:105)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James K. Harmon, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:106)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Missouri Harmon, Melfa, Virginia, 1933-1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:107)
      - Correspondence to Walter Harper of The Virginia Pilot, Norfolk, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:108)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. Bascom Harrell, Washington, D.C., 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:109)
      - Correspondence from R. N. Harris, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:110)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Walter Edward Harris, Petersburg, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:111)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. R. Harris, Lara, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:112)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Burbage Harrison, Berlin, Maryland, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:113)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Dabney C. Harrison, Boyce, Clarke County, Virginia, 1925, 1929., 6 items. (Box-folder 3:114)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. F. Harrison, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:115)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Orlando Harrison, Berlin, Maryland, 1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:116)
      - Correspondence from Pat Harrison, New York, New York, 1928., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:117)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mack B. Hart, Richmond, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:118)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. W. Hart, Poulson, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:119)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James H. Hartman, Temperanceville, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:120)
      - Duplicate correspondence with R. N. Hartness, Ettrick-Petersburg, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:121)
      - Correspondence from W. Eugene Harvey, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:122)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence to A. R. Harwood, Appomattox, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:123)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Samuel C. Hatcher, Ashland, Virginia, 1925-1935., 6 items. (Box-folder 3:124)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Oscar L. Hatton, Severna Park, Maryland, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:125)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Horace A. Hawkins, Richmond Evening Journal, Richmond, Virginia, 1914-1925., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:126)
      - Correspondence from W. H. Hawkins, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:127)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James M. Hayes, Richmond, Virginia, 1918-1924., 6 items. (Box-folder 3:128)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Josephy E. Healy, Mathews, Virginia, 1924., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:129)
      - Correspondence from T. M. Hearn, Franklin City, Virginia, 1895-1896., 12 items. (Box-folder 3:130)
      - Correspondence from H. E. Hearne, Onancock, Virginia, 1920., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:131)
      - Duplicate correspondence to T. J. C. Heath, Petersburg, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:132)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. R. Henderson, Nandua, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:133)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Norvell L. Henley, Richmond, Virginia, 1920., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:134)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James G. Hening, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:135)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence David Hepburn, Assistant Superintendent, Anti-Saloon League of Virginia, 1918-1928., 26 items. (Box-folder 3:136)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. E. Herbert, Norfolk, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:137)
      - Duplicate correspondence from Thomas Herbert, Crozet, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:138)
      - Telegram from John Hershberg, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:139)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. T. Hickman, Painter, Virginia, 1911-1935., 6 items. (Box-folder 3:140)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Floyd E. Hickman, Horntown, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:141)
      - Correspondence from J. H. Hickman, Pastoria, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:142)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mary Louise Hickman, Painter, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:143)
      - Correspondence from Milton T. Hickman, Painter, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:144)
      - Correspondence from J. H. Hiden, Pungoteague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:145)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Ella Higginbotham, Buena Vista, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:146)
      - Correspondence from Edgar T. Higgins, New York, New York, 1932., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:147)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Marianna P. Higgins, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:148)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Ben Hilliard, White Stone, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:149)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. M. Hillman, St. Paul, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:150)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William T. Hodges, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:151)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George B. Hoffman, Exmore, Virginia, 1912., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:152)
      - Correspondence to J. W. Hogan, Snells, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:153)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mr. And Mrs. Henry J. Hoge, Hamilton, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:154)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. M. Hoge, Lincoln, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:155)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mrs. Howard M. Hoge, WCTU [Women's Christian Temperance Union], Lincoln, Virginia, 1922-1928., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:156)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mary J. Hogsett, Washington, D.C., 1911., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:157)
      - Correspondence from Robert A. Hogsett, Jacksonville, Florida, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:158)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Hogshire Tent and Awning Co., Norfolk, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:159)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. W. Holland, Eastville, Maryland, 1911-1929., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:160)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John W. K. Holland, Onley, Virginia, 1927, 1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:161)
      - Correspondence from J. P. Holland, Norfolk, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:162)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George J. Holliday, Galivants Ferry, South Carolina, 1922-1935., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:163)
      - Telegram from J. W. Holloway, Smithfield, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:164)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. G. Holman, Greensboro, North Carolina, 1925-1927., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:165)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. E. Holstein, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:166)
      - Correspondence from H. H. Holt, [1918]., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:167)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Henry W. Holt, Staunton, Virginia, 1922, 1924., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:168)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Saxon W. Holt, Newport News, Virginia, 1924, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:169)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Home for Confederate Women, Richmond, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:170)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Lester Hooker, Stuart and Richmond, Virginia, 1922, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:171)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. Murray Hooker, 5th District Congressman and State Chairman, Democratic party, 1922-1929., 19 items. (Box-folder 3:172)
      - Correspondence from A. T. Hope, Hopeton, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:173)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Susan Jane Hope, Nelsonia, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:174)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Hopkins and Borther, Onancock, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:175)
      - Correspondence from Evelyn P. Hopkins, Onancock, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:176)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Geo. J. Hopkins, Baltimore, Maryland, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:177)
      - Duplicate correspondence to John P. L. Hopkins, Onancock, Virginia, [1911]., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:178)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William E. Hopkins, Onancock, Virginia, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:179)
      - Correspondence from Henry S. Horkheimer, Baltimore, Maryland, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:180)
      - Correspondence from J. R. Horsley, Stapleton, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:181)
      - Correspondence from J. D. Hosler, Irvington, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:182)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. T. Hoskins, Millers Tavern, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:183)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. W. Hough, Anti-Saloon League, Norfolk, Virginia, 1914., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:184A)
      - Correspondence from Cornelia F. House, Buffalo, New York, 1930., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:184B)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Andrew J. Howarth, 1933-1935., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:185)
      - Correspondence from J. F. Howison, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:186)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Dr. and Mrs. P. W. Howie, Richmond, Virginia, 1918-1933., 6 items. (Box-folder 3:187)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. T. Huckstep, Columbia, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:188)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. W. Hodgins, Chase City, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:189)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. B. Hunt, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:190)
      - Duplicate correspondence to N. F. Hunt, Accomac, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:191)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. R. Hutcheson, Boydton, Virginia, 1928-1929., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:192)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. R. Hutchinson, Harborton, Virginia, 1924-1932., 5 items. (Box-folder 3:193)
      - Correspondence from E. N. Hutchinson, New church and Massey, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:194)
      - Correspondence from Ellis Hutchinson, Drummandtown, Virginia, [1901?]., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:195)
      - Correspondence from G. O. Hutchinson, Wardtown, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:196)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John R. Hutchinson, Blacksburg, Virginia, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:197)
      - Ccorrespondence with M. A. Hutchinson, Richmond, Virginia, 1925-1931., 34 items. (Box-folder 3:198-199)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with M. A. Hutchinson, Richmond, Virginia, 1925-1928., 9 items. (Box-folder 3:198)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with M. A. Hutchinson, Richmond, Virginia, 1929-1931., 25 items. (Box-folder 3:199)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Frank Hyslop, Keller, Virginia, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:200)
      - Duplicate correspondence to William H. Hyslop, Craddockville, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:201)
      - Correspondence to Clarence J. Hyslop, Blacksburg, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:202)
      - Correspondence with persons whose surnames begin with "H", 1911, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:203)
      - Duplicate correspondence from the International Agricultural Corp., Norfolk, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:204)
      - Correspondence from the International Company of America, Baltimore, Maryland, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:205)
      - Correspondence from Henry Jackson, Danville, Kentucky, 1910-1911., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:206)
      - Correspondence from A. G. James, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:207)
      - Correspondence from B. O. James, Richmond, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:208)
      - Correspondence from H. A. James, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:209)
      - Correspondence from Reverend M. James, New York, New York, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:210)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Rorer A. James, Jr., Danville, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:211)
      - Correspondence with R. M. Janney, Gloucester, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:212)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. M. Janney, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1918, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:213)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. L. Jarman, Farmville, Virginia, 1922, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:214)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John G. Jefferson, Amelia, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:215)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John G. Jefferson, Amelia, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:216)
      - Correspondence from Otis P. Jefferson, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:217)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Daniel Jeffries, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920, 1931., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:218)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. L. and W. H. Jeffreys, Chase City, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:219)
      - Correspondence from Miss J. S. Jennings, Washington, D.C., 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:220)
      - Correspondence from Livingston S. Jennings, New York, 1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:221)
      - Correspondence from W. E. Jenson, Westerville, Ohio, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:222)
      - Correspondence from K. J. Jester, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:223)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Louis T. Jester, Newport News, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:224)
      - Correspondence from T. A. Jett, Beedville, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:225)
      - Correspondence from Georgia May Jobson, Richmond, Virginia, 1912, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:226)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. W. Johnsson, Gates City, Virginia, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:227)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Branch Johnson, Richmond, Virginia, 1920-1931., 12 items. (Box-folder 3:228)
      - Correspondence from G. L. H. Johnson, Staunton, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:229)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Hiram Johnson, Washington, D.C., 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:230)
      - Correspondence from J. E. Johnson, New Church, Virginia, 1911., 2 item. (Box-folder 3:231)
      - Correspondence from J. T. Johnson, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:232)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with James W. Johnson, Norfolk, Virginia, 1918., 10 items. (Box-folder 3:233)
      - Correspondence from John D. Johnson, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:234)
      - Correspondence with John Henry Johnson, Office of the Auditor of Public Accounts, Richmond, Virginia, 1912-1929., 76 items. (Box-folder 3:235-240)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Henry Johnson, 1912-1927., 9 items. (Box-folder 3:235)
        - Duplication and original correspondence with John Henry Johnson, 1928., 13 items. (Box-folder 3:236)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Henry Johnson, January 1929., 13 items. (Box-folder 3:237)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Henry Johnson, February 1929., 11 items. (Box-folder 3:238)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Henry Johnson, March 1929., 13 items. (Box-folder 3:239)
        - Duplicate and original correspondence with John Henry Johnson, April-December 1929., 17 items. (Box-folder 3:240)
      - Correspondence from Mrs. L. Johnson, Craddockville, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:241)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Minnie Johnson, Painter, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:242)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Susie Johnson, Onancock, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:243)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. T. Johnson, Horntown, Virginia, 1906-1922., 7 items. (Box-folder 3:244)
      - Correspondence from T. C. Johnson, Norfolk, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:245)